http://www.moca.org/about/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
The Museum of Contemporary Art (“MOCA”) is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our website (moca.org), our online store (store.moca.org), and our social media properties, including all data, information and compilations on any of the foregoing (collectively referred to as the “MOCA website”) and to disclosing to you how the information you provide when using the MOCA website will be used. By accessing the MOCA website or engaging in any transaction on the MOCA website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy without limitation or qualification. If you do not wish to be bound by this Privacy Policy, do not access the MOCA website and do not submit any information to the MOCA website. There is a link to this policy in the footer on every page of the MOCA website.
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information
MOCA uses the personal information you provide to us for internal purposes, such as completing and tracking your transaction, analyzing trends, and collecting statistics. MOCA may also compile and provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third parties.  Except as provided herein, the statistics shared with third parties will not include any personally identifying information.
We may share the names, postal addresses, email addresses, and social media accounts we receive from visitors, members and donors with other nonprofit organizations. If you do not want to have your information used in this way, you must send an email message containing your name and postal address to membership@moca.org with the subject “Do Not Use Personal Data.” We may also share information about our members and donors with third-party vendors who help us analyze and understand our donor and membership base.
After you make a purchase on the MOCA online store, we may share your name and postal address—but not your email address—with other organizations or companies whose products might be of interest to you. The policies of these organizations and companies may differ from ours. If you do not want to have your information used in this way, you must send an email message containing your name and postal address to membership@moca.org with the subject “Do Not Use Personal Data.”
MOCA may disclose account information to any third party when such disclosure is reasonably necessary to either (i) comply with the law; (ii) enforce the terms of any of our user agreements, including without limitation this Privacy Policy; or (iii) protect the rights, property, and safety of MOCA, the users of its site, or others.
If you have provided us with your email address, we may send you emails in order to alert you to information, events, activities, or programs at or related to MOCA that we believe may be of interest to you, or to alert you about MOCA store sales or other promotional events at MOCA. If you do not want us to use your email address to contact you for these purposes, you must send an email message containing your name and postal address to membership@moca.org with the subject “Do Not Use Personal Data.”
We may combine information you give to us online, offline, in our stores, through your membership or donation, at any of MOCA’s physical locations, or through our catalogs. We also may combine or supplement this information with publicly available information and additional information we receive from or have cross-referenced with our third-party vendors and others. We use this combined information to enhance and personalize your experience with us; to communicate with you about ways to donate to the museum, products, exhibitions, or events that may be of interest to you; or for other promotional or MOCA-related purposes.
Use of Outside Vendors
MOCA retains qualified third-party service providers to help us manage the MOCA website and allow us to better serve our visitors and customers. These include third-party contractors who assist us by processing registration and ticketing for MOCA and for certain events or courses. We also engage third-party vendors to analyze the information we collect on the MOCA website and through other resources for marketing or similar purposes. We also use third-party service providers to process your payment transactions and detect possible fraudulent use of a payment card. These service providers receive the information you enter into our website, and information about your payment card, purchase, mobile device, computer, software and their location for fraud detection purposes. You agree to the disclosure of your personal information to these third-party service providers for this purpose. MOCA requires its vendors to maintain the security of the information to which they are provided access and restricts the vendors from using the information in any way not expressly authorized by MOCA.
We may contract with third parties who use cookies, and other online tracking technologies to collect information on our behalf. These parties are contractually required to maintain the confidentiality of this information. If you would like to opt out of this use of your information, you can change the preferences of your browser so that it does not accept cookies. We may contract with companies or others to provide certain services, including data management, promotional services, etc. We provide these service providers with the information they need to perform these services, but we restrict the vendors from using the information in any way not expressly authorized by MOCA.
Although MOCA requires its third-party vendors and service providers to maintain the security of the information to which they are provided access and restricts the vendors and service providers from using the information in any way not expressly authorized by MOCA, MOCA cannot guarantee, and is not liable for, the security of its third-party vendors and service providers.  You agree to release MOCA of all liability for (i) any breach or flaw in the security of the information systems of the third-party vendors and services providers; and (ii) any misuse or misappropriation of your personal information by any of the third-party vendors and service providers.
Security
The MOCA website uses various measures designed to secure information. If you prefer, you may also place a MOCA Store order by phone at  (213) 621-1710. For membership gifts, and donations, you may call (213) 621-1794.
Be sure to use a known and trusted secure connection and to log off when finished using a shared computer. Be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
Please be advised that when placing an online order through the MOCA online store, your personal data will be protected in accordance with United States law, but may not be given the same level of protection legally required in the European Union.
DESPITE OUR REASONABLE EFFORTS TO PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, WE CANNOT ENSURE OR WARRANT THE SECURITY OF ANY INFORMATION TRANSMITTED TO MOCA AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU DISCLOSE TO US IS AT YOUR OWN RISK.
Cookies
Cookies are small files of information that are stored on your computer’s hard drive by your Web browser. The cookies we use do not contain any personal information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change the preferences of your browser so that it does not accept them. In order to use all the features of the MOCA website, we recommend that you accept cookies.
Linking
The MOCA website may include links to websites operated by third parties over which we have no control. Once you leave the MOCA website, this Privacy Policy will not apply, and you access such sites at your own risk.
Data Storage
Online Retail Purchases
When you order a product from the MOCA online store, we need to know your name, billing and shipping addresses, telephone number, email address, and credit card information to process your order. Your credit card information will be stored on a secure server and used only as needed to process your transaction. It will also be sent to our third-party payment card processors and service providers to perform fraud detection and payment processing services. If your purchase is rejected by our website because it was detected as a possible fraudulent use of a payment card, and you are in fact the authorized user of the card, you can contact us at storeonline@moca.org or call (213) 621-1710 for the issue to be evaluated and resolved. We will retain your personally identifiable information for our records, in order to facilitate better customer service, and to inform you of our products and promotional offers.
Online Memberships and Donations
When you purchase a MOCA membership or make a donation to MOCA online, we will ask you to provide us with the information we need to process your membership and/or to acknowledge your contribution. This information includes your name, billing and mailing addresses, telephone number, email address, and credit card information. Your credit card information will be stored on a secure server and used only as needed to process your transaction. It will also be sent to our third-party payment card processors and service providers to perform fraud detection and payment processing services. If your purchase or donation is rejected by our website because it was detected as a possible fraudulent use of a payment card, and you are in fact the authorized user of the card, you can contact us at membership@moca.org or call (213) 621-1794 for the issue to be evaluated and resolved. We will retain your personally identifiable information for our records, in order to facilitate better stewardship of your donation. To process payments for members who have selected automatic renewal, MOCA will also retain payment information, in a secure manner, until such time that either the payment information expires (when we will contact you to update it), or the auto-renewal of the membership is canceled by you. In certain cases, you may be asked for additional information to complete your request, such as the names and birth dates (month/year) of your children if obtaining a Family membership or any Contributing membership with children (see “Children 16 and under”).
Online purchases of Museum admission tickets, event tickets, and course registrations
MOCA uses third-party vendors to administer and process your online purchase of admission tickets to MOCA’s physical properties. We also work with third-party contractors to process ticketing for certain events or registration for certain courses. MOCA requires its vendors to maintain the security of the information which you provide to them and restricts the vendors from using this information in any way not expressly authorized by MOCA (see “Use of outside vendors” above).
Online Surveys
MOCA may invite you to participate in surveys posted on the MOCA website or sent to you by email. You may decide whether you wish to complete such surveys, which may ask about your background, occupation, or similar questions. We use this information to help us better understand our audience, which in turn allows us to better meet your needs and interests. Information collected in these surveys is never sold, rented, or shared with third parties for marketing purposes, but we may share it with outside vendors to analyze the information we collect (see “Use of outside vendors” above).
Online Contests
MOCA will occasionally offer visitors the opportunity to participate in online contests or sweepstakes. If you choose to enter, you may need to provide your name and email address so that we may contact you in connection with the contest. We may also request that you provide us with certain other information, such as your zip code, state of residence, and grade in school (provided that you are at least 16 years of age).
MOCA Newsletters
MOCA offers visitors to the MOCA website the opportunity to subscribe to one or more of our online newsletters, a service hosted by a third-party contractor that has agreed to use the email address you provide only to send newsletters to you. If you choose to subscribe, you will receive MOCA newsletters on the topics you choose. You may subscribe or unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions on the newsletter.
Emailing MOCA
If you send an email to MOCA, your message and email address may be saved and we may send you emails in order to respond to your message. Any material, business information, ideas, concepts, or other information sent to MOCA by email will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. We will only use the information provided in your email and your email address to improve the MOCA website, services, and products, and to fulfill or respond to your requests for products, services, or information.
Children 16 and Under
MOCA does not solicit or knowingly collect personal information from children 16 years of age and younger. Visitors 16 years of age and under are required to obtain an adult’s permission before accessing or using the MOCA website.
Revisions to our Privacy Policy
Please note that MOCA may revise its Privacy Policy at any time, without notice, such changes to be effective immediately upon posting on the MOCA website. Such revisions may arise in response to changes in the law, policy, or other factors. We encourage you to periodically visit this page to review our most current policy.
Last update: September 1, 2018
Contacting Us
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below:
By email:
info@moca.org
By telephone:
(213) 626-6222
Info
Info
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The Museum of Contemporary Art (“MOCA”) is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our website (moca.org), our online store (store.moca.org), and our social media properties, including all data, information and compilations on any of the foregoing (collectively referred to as the “MOCA website”) and to disclosing to you how the information you provide when…
